You must have heard the saying that one's profit is the other's loss and the other
's profit is generally a saying
but look at it in reality as well and
here there are two banks, one profitable and the other active, so
how the
loss of one bank is the profit of the other bank and
both are huge giant banks like elephants in themselves,
come and do a complete analysis of this
Arya Devanshi Amar, tell me such a device with
you, which bank has suffered a loss and how the
other bank took advantage of its loss,
explain it in full detail, Pimple, you
see, we will talk about FICCI and we all
know that in December 2017 itself, RBI had
banned the first class banks, due to this the way
more damage was done to the banks, that is,
technicalities and digitization, now
due to this the ban on starting new work was
seen and it is still continuing, so continuously
we will see that their market capitalization
seems to be decreasing, this is
also the reason and at this
time we have to see but such a huge
loss is seen because the
last bank Coin had the highest market
share in the credit card business but
now  It seems to be gradually decreasing,
so the loss is being seen only through these tips.
Where it is seen that
there was a ban on their chocolate juice,
but now this benefit
seems to be accruing to the bank because
gradually, continuously, we are seeing that the other
banks are now offering credit cards
and their market share is gradually increasing.
Till last year, there were not many features in the IS Bank credit card,
but now their market share is
gradually increasing.
They have also signed an agreement with Amazon, and due to this,
they seem to be getting a lot of benefit.
Looking at the behavior of the bank in the credit card business from the CG Singer Maa area,
if we talk about the last 9 months, then
about 10 lakh rupees have been released for the bank
and now see, between November 2021,
about 11 crore rupees have been released at
11.30 pm,
with which now see this development
shows them also getting continuous benefit.  There are six and a half
crore jokes, yes if they were seen being discussed here then
they would also be shown getting profit here, so
overall now see, two
companies and Rinku are seen getting profit,
first of all these useless ones who
talked continuously, but this time
in the last two-three years we have seen that there has been a continuous
growth, it would have been of such banks, show this, so
gradually their business was also on, show that